One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Knock-Up Stream
Yukarı Fırlatan Akıntı
Where the heck is he?! It's already morning!
Nerede kaldı bu?! Sabah oldu bile!
He's forty-six minutes late! We're going to miss the current!
Tam 46 dakika gecikti! Akıntıyı kaçıracağız!
With all that heavy gold, it'd take him even longer to come back!
O kadar altını da taşıması lazım, kim bilir ne kadar gecikecek!
There's no way he took that into consideration!
İmkânı yok onu düşünmemiştir bile!
No, I don't think the time was ever a consideration for him here.
Hayır, muhtemelen zamanı hiç planlamadı.
Yeah, 100 percent.
Evet, kesin öyle.
Do you think he got beat up?
Sence Luffy yenildi mi?
By that Bellamy guy?!
Bellamy denen herife mi?!
If he did, time would be the least of his problems!
Eğer yenildiyse, gecikmesi onun son problemi olacak!
What the hell, Nami?
Derdin ne senin be?
Hey!
Hey!
It's him! Thank goodness! He's back!
İşte geldi! Şükürler olsun! Döndü!
I did it!
Başardım!
Hurry up, Luffy! We're behind schedule!
Acele et, Luffy! Programımızın gerisindeyiz!
Check it out!
Baksanıza!
A Hercules! It took forever to find one!
Herkül böceği! Bulmam uzun sürdü!
You were looking...
Böcek mi...
...for a beetle?!
...arıyordun?!
Whoa! Awesome!
Oha! Harika!
The Going Merry: Flight Mode!
Going Merry: Uçuş Versiyonu!
It looks like it can fly!
Cidden uçacak gibi!
Right?! It's all thanks to them!
Değil mi?! Onlara teşekkür et!
Look at 'em go.
Görmezden gelin.
I get uneasy just looking at it...
Bakınca bile tadım kaçıyor...
Same here.
Benim de.
Even a pigeon would've been better than a chicken...
Güvercin bile tavuktan iyi bir seçim olurdu...
You think that's the issue?! You're an idiot!
Sorun sence o mu?! Amma aptalsın!
Alright! Let's set sail! Is everyone ready?!
Pekâlâ! Hadi yelken açalım! Herkes hazır mı?!
– Aye aye, sir!
– Hay hay, efendim!
Get on board already! There's no time!
Gemiye bin! Vakit kalmadı!
Or do you wanna waste your only ticket into the sky, you fool?
Yoksa gökyüzüne olan tek biletini yakmak mı istiyorsun, aptal?
Right! Thanks for the ship!
Pekâlâ! Gemi için teşekkürler!
It's them you should thank.
Asıl onlara teşekkür et.
Yeah! Thanks, you guys!
Evet! Teşekkürler!
My Hercules... is yours!
Herkül böceğim sizin olsun!
– Really?! For us?! – Seriously?!
– Gerçekten mi?! Bizim mi?! – Gerçekten mi?!
– What a great guy!
– Ne kadar iyi biri!
Anyway, we gotta go! Get on board before it's too late!
Neyse, artık gitmeliyiz! Çok geç olmadan gemiye bin!
We'll lead the way, so follow us!
Biz önden gideceğiz, bizi takip edin!
Luffy! Hurry!
Luffy! Acele et!
Yeah!
Tamam!
That "City of Gold" is just a figment of Noland's imagination!
O "Altın Şehir" sadece Noland'ın hayal ürünüydü!
Saruyama Alliance!
Saruyama İttifakı!
Don't screw this up!
Bu işi berbat etmeyin!
No matter what happens, we'll back them up with everything we've got!
Bu tayfa için elinizden gelen her şeyi yapın!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Alright! Let's go!
Pekâlâ! Gidelim!
Everyone, time to set sail!
Millet, yelken açma zamanı!
All right!
İşte bu!
Aye, Nami dearest!
Başüstüne, Nami-tan!
This is where we part ways, kid!
Burada yollarımız ayrılıyor, çocuk!
Yeah!
Evet!
There's one thing that I know for sure.
Kesin olarak bildiğim bir şey var.
Huh?
Ha?
No one has ever disproved the existence of the City of Gold or the sky island.
Hiç kimse Altın Şehir'in veya gökyüzü adasının varlığını kanıtlayamadı.
Right!
Evet!
People might laugh at my faulty logic, but it's good enough for me.
İnsanlar bunlara gülüp saçma desin, benim için sorun değil.
That's what romance is!
İşte romantizm budur!
Romance...
Romantizm...
That's right!
Aynen öyle!
Thanks for the gold.
Altın için teşekkürler.
Don't go falling from the sky now, alright?!
Gökyüzünden düşmeyin, tamam mı?!
See ya, chestnut head!
Görüşürüz, kestane kafa!
Thanks for everything, Cricket!
Her şey için teşekkürler, Cricket-san!
Mister, the City of Gold definitely exists!
Bayım, eminim Altın Şehir gerçektir!
Chestnut head! Don't do anything reckless!
Kestane kafa! Kendini çok zorlama!
Mind your own business!
Kendi işine bak!
It's morning already!
Sabah oldu bile!
Well? See anything?
Pekâlâ? Bir şey görüyor musun?
I can't see any trace of the shore yet!
Henüz kıyıyı bile göremiyorum!
Are those guys really going to the sky island?
Gerçekten gökyüzü adasına mı gidiyorlar?
Yeah, that's what they said.
Evet, öyle dediler.
It'll be tough to follow 'em, so let's settle things before that.
Onları takip etmek zor olacak, o yüzden şimdiden işlerini bitirelim.
Listen up! It's seven o'clock!
Dinleyin! Saat 7!
We should arrive at our destination around eleven!
Saat 11'de hedefimize varmış olacağız!
Like the boss said, the Knock-Up Stream's exact location
Patronun dediği gibi Yukarı Fırlatan Akıntı'nın yeri her seferinde değişiyor,
changes each time, so we need to arrive early to find it!
o yüzden alana erken varıp yerini tespit etmemiz gerekiyor!
Look! Look!
Bakın! Bakın!
We're a little behind schedule, so...
Programın biraz gerisindeyiz, o yüzden...
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Hey! Beni dinliyor musunuz?
See! It looked forward!
Bakın! İleri baktı!
There sure are some weird birds out there!
Ne garip kuşlar var!
It's true! He can only face south! This guy's a compass! How funny!
Doğruymuş! Sadece güneye bakabiliyor! Bu eleman pusula gibi! Çok komik!
What'd he say?
Ne dedi?
He said he's going to face a different direction to mess us up.
"Farklı bir yöne bakıp işinizi berbat edeceğim" dedi.
Go ahead and try!
Denesene!
Oh! He faced north!
Ah! Kuzeye baktı!
He only feels right when facing south!
Güneye bakmadan içi rahat etmiyor!
Hey, you guys! Don't make the big boss mad!
Hey, çocuklar! Büyük patronu kızdırmayın!
Leave them be! Though their antics do make me nervous.
Boş verin onları! Onlarla uğraşırsak işimize odaklanamayız!
Huh? What's wrong?
Ha? Sorun nedir?
There's no point in being anxious!
Kaygılanmanın faydası yok!
Let's take it easy!
Rahatlayın biraz!
And who put us behind schedule?
Peki kimin yüzünden programın gerisindeyiz?
He's right! There's no point in being tense for hours on end!
O haklı! Gergin olmanın kimseye faydası yok!
I see! Right, men! Full speed ahead, while relaxing!
Anladım! Pekâlâ! Tam yol ileri ama rahat bir şekilde!
What nice weather!
Hava ne güzel!
Are we gonna be okay?
Bu işi becerebilecek miyiz?
Boss! Bad news!
Patron! Kötü haberlerim var!
What's wrong?!
Sorun nedir?!
Night's coming from the southwest! Cumuloimperator clouds!
Güneybatı yönünden gece yaklaşıyor! İmparator kümülüs!
Seriously?! What time is it?!
Gerçekten mi?! Saat kaç?!
Ten o'clock! Way earlier than expected!
Saat 10! Beklediğimizden çok daha erken bu!
This is bad... Can we make it, Shojo?!
Bu hiç iyi değil... Başarabilecek miyiz, Shojo?
Utan Divers! Into the sea immediately!
Utan Dalgıçları! Hemen denize!
Look for currents!
Akıntıyı tespit edin!
It's the cumuloimperator clouds!
İmparator kümülüs!
What's happening?!
Ne oluyor?!
They appeared sooner than expected, and we still don't know where the current is!
Beklediğimizden daha erken belirdi. Ama daha akıntının yerini bilmiyoruz!
The sonar pinged! Large current detected at twelve o'clock!
Yankı doğrulandı! Saat 12 yönünde, dev bir akıntı bulundu!
Large unidentified creature at nine o'clock! I believe it's a sea king!
Saat 9 yönünde, dev bir yaratık belirlendi! Muhtemelen deniz kralı!
Waves clashing against the current at ten o'clock!
Saat 10 yönünde, akıntıya ters hareket eden dalga belirlendi!
Likely a giant whirlpool!
Muhtemelen dev bir girdap!
That's it! Point the ship toward ten o'clock!
İşte bu! Pruvayı saat 10 yönüne çevirin!
It's an indication of the explosion! Catch the whirlpool! Don't let up!
Patlama olacağının belirtisi bu! Girdabı yakalayın! Geri çekilmeyin!
What the...?!
Ne olu...?!
The waves suddenly got taller!
Dalgalar aniden yükseldi!
We're gonna sink!
Alabora olacağız!
It's the earthquake before the explosion! Get ready!
Patlama öncesi depremi bu! Hazır olun!
E-Explosion?!
P-Patlama mı?!
Miss Navigator!
Rotacı Hanım!
What's the log pose saying?
Seyir Pusulası ne diyor!
It keeps pointing to those clouds!
O bulutu gösteriyor!
The sky island is up there?!
Gökyüzü adası tam üstümüzde mi?!
The wind's perfect, too!
Rüzgâr da tam istediğimiz yönde!
The clouds are headed for the heart of the whirlpool!
İmparator kümülüs girdaba doğru geliyor!
Wait! What whirlpool? Where do you see one?
Bekleyin! Ne girdabı? Nerede gördünüz girdabı?
Looks like we hit the jackpot this time, Brother!
Görünüşe göre hedefi tam on ikiden vurduk kardeşim!
Yeah! The explosion looks like it'll be big enough, too!
Evet! Patlama da yeterince büyük olacak gibi görünüyor!
So we can make it?!
Yani başaracak mıyız?!
We sure can!
Elbette!
Huh?
Ha?
We'll get you into the whirlpool's vortex!
Sizi girdabın içine doğru çekeceğiz!
What do we do after that?!
Sonra ne yapacağız?!
Ride the current! If you can get to the center, things should work out!
Akıntıda ilerleyin! Girdabın merkezine gidebilirseniz iyi olacaksınız!
The center of this massive whirlpool?!
Bu devasa girdabın merkezine mi?!
Nobody said anything about being sucked in!
Kimse bununla ilgili bir şey söylemedi!
It's all right! I'll protect you and Robin!
Sorun değil, Nami-san! Seni ve Robin-chan'ı koruyacağım!
I've never seen such a large whirlpool...
Böyle bir girdap ilk defa görüyorum...
Holy crap! This is bad! Let's turn back! Let me go back!
Lanet olsun! Bu hiç iyi değil! Geri dönelim! Bırakın geri döneyim!
Just accept it, Usopp! It's too late. Someone is already sucked in.
Koyver gitsin, Usopp! Artık geri dönüş yok. Girdaba girdik bile.
Let's go! Sky island!
Gidelim! Gökyüzü adasına!
Alright, you guys!
Pekâlâ çocuklar!
You're on your own now! Good luck!
Gerisi sizde! Bol şans!
Right! Thanks for the lift!
Tamam! Yardımınız için teşekkürler!
Hold on!
Bekleyin!
Let me off, will you?! I'm scared out of my wits here!
Beni de alın! Korkudan öleceğim!
Let me go back, you jerk!
Bırakın da geri döneyim!
We're all gonna die!
Hepimiz öleceğiz!
Nobody said anything about a giant whirlpool! They tricked us!
Kimse bana dev girdaptan bahsetmedi! Bizi kandırdılar!
It's night!
Gece oldu!
The whirlpool is sucking us in really fast!
Girdap bizi içine çekiyor!
Let's go back, Luffy! We still have time!
Geri dönelim, Luffy! Hâlâ vaktimiz var!
Don't you understand?! This whirlpool alone is enough to kill us!
Anlamıyor musun?! Bu girdap bile bizi öldürmeye yeter!
The sky island's a dream within a dream!
Gökyüzü adası, hayal içinde hayal!
A dream within a dream? You think so?
Hayal içinde hayal mi? Cidden öyle mi düşünüyorsun?
Yes, Luffy! I don't think we can do this after all!
Evet, Luffy! Bunu gerçekten başarabileceğimizi sanmıyorum!
An island in a dream within a dream!
Hayal içinde hayal bir ada!
I'd never forgive myself for passing up an adventure like that!
Böyle bir macerayı kaçırırsam kendimi asla affetmem!
– H-He's enjoying this...
– Ç-Çok mutlu görünüyor...
Hey! While you guys are over here pointlessly whining...
Hey! Siz orada sızlanırken...
Yeah? What?
Ha? Ne?
We're being pulled into it!
İçine çekiliyoruz!
Now, Nami! Seek shelter in my arms!
Şimdi, Nami-san! Kollarımda teselli bul!
We're falling in!
İçine düşüyoruz!
What?! It disappeared?! How come?!
Ne?! Yok mu oldu?! Nasıl?!
What happened?!
Ne oldu?!
Th-That huge whirlpool... What's going on here?!
O dev girdap... Ne oluyor böyle?!
No! It's already started!
Hayır! Çoktan başladı!
Huh?
Ha?
The whirlpool just vanished!
Girdap kayboldu!
Y-You don't mean...
Y-Yani...
Hold it!
Durun!
Hey, Zoro!
Hey, Zoro!
Look!
Bak!
I caught up to ya, Straw Hat Luffy!
Seni yakaladık, Hasır Şapkalı Luffy!
He was in Mock Town...!
Mock Şehri'ndeki herif...!
Who?!
Kim o?!
I came to collect that 100-million head of yours! Prepare yourself!
100 milyonluk kelleni almaya geldim! Hazır ol!
Hey, who are they? Friends of yours?
Hey, kim bunlar? Arkadaşlarınız mı?
Huh, I dunno.
Ha, bilmiyorum.
Why's it dark around here?
Burası niye karanlık?
My head? What do you mean, 100 million?
Ödülüm mü? Ne 100 milyonu?
So you don't know!
Demek bilmiyorsun!
There's a 100-million-belly bounty on your head!
Kellene 100 milyon beli ödül biçilmiş!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro! You're worth 60 million!
Ve sen Korsan Avcısı Zoro! Sen de 60 milyon değerindesin!
It's true! Those are new wanted posters.
Bu doğru! Onlar yeni aranıyor posterleri.
Zoro! You're a wanted man now!
Zoro! Sağlam ödülün var artık ha!
What?! Hold on! What about me?! There's one for me too, right?!
Ne?! Dur bakalım! Ya ben?! Benim de var değil mi?!
Uh... nope.
Ah... senin yok.
Look closer!
Dikkatli bak!
Not there.
Yok.
That makes sense. Your bounties must've shot up after the Alabasta incident!
Mantıklı. Alabasta'dan sonra ödüllerinizin böyle fırlaması normal.
But 100 million...!
Ama 100 milyon...!
One hundred million!
100 milyon!
Hear that?! I'm worth 100 million!
Duydunuz mu?! 100 milyon değerindeyim!
And I'm at 60 million! Pretty lame, huh?
60 milyon demek, baya hayal kırıklığı!
You shouldn't be celebrating that!
Bu kutlanacak şey mi?!
Hey, you guys! Don't get distracted!
Hey, çocuklar! Dikkatiniz dağılmasın!
It's coming! The Knock-Up Stream!
Geliyor! Yukarı Fırlatan Akıntı!
Get ready!
Hazır olun!
What the...?
Ne olu...?
All hands! Hold on tight or get in the cabin!
Herkes gemiye tutunsun veya içeri girsin!
The ship is going up!
Gemi yükseliyor!
No good! The ship's gonna capsize!
Eyvah! Gemi alabora olacak!
Everyone, grab on!
Herkes tutunsun!
Don't get thrown overboard!
Sakın düşmeyin!
– Go! To the sky island!
– Gidin! Gökyüzü adasına...!
What the heck's going on?!
Ne oluyor lan böyle?!
The ship's going straight up a pillar of water!
Gemi akıntının üzerinde düşey olarak ilerliyor!
This is fun!
Çok eğlenceli!
How is this possible?!
Bu nasıl mümkün olabilir?!
Wind?!
Rüzgâr mı?!
Alright! We can get to the sky now! Go, Merry!
Pekâlâ! şimdi gökyüzüne gidebiliriz! Hadi, Merry!
Hold on! I don't think it's gonna be that easy!
Dur bakalım! Sanırım o kadar kolay olmayacak!
Wh-What's wrong?!
N-Ne oldu?!
Huh? Did we forget something?
Ha? Bir şey mi atladık?
The hull's coming clear of the water!
Gemi sudan ayırlıyor!
Huh?!
Ha?!
If this keeps up, we're gonna get sent flying to our doom!
Böyle giderse, ölümümüze doğru düşeceğiz!
B-B-But what do you w-want us to do?! W-W-We can barely even h-hold on!
A-A-A-Ama ne yapmamızı istiyorsun?! Z-Z-Z-Zar zor tutunuyoruz zaten!
Huh?! What's that?!
Ha?! O ne?!
A sea king!
Deniz kralı!
It's the one that got sucked in earlier!
Girdap tarafından yutulmuştu!
See! It's only a matter of time before that happens to us too!
Gördünüz mü?! Aynı şey her an bizim başımıza da gelebilir!
You say that, but we are riding on a hell of an explosion!
Öyle diyorsun ama patlamanın etkisine kapılmış durumdayız!
Can we really help it?!
Ne yapabiliriz ki?!
This is a natural disaster after all!
Doğal afet bu sonuçta!
There's a bunch of stuff falling on us!
Bir şeyler düşüyor!
It's the victims of the Knock-Up Stream!
Yukarı Fırlatan Akıntı'nın kurbanları!
We're goners! We're gonna slam into the sea and die!
İşimiz bitti! Denize çakılıp öleceğiz!
Spread the sails right now!
Yelkenleri açın! Hemen şimdi!
This is the sea, not just any water pillar! It's a rising ocean current!
Bu önünde sonunda bir deniz! Sudan bir kule değil! Yükselen bir akıntı!
And the updraft is a rising air current
Ve altımızdan esen rüzgâr da...
produced by the geothermal heat and steam explosion!
jeotermal ısı ve buhar patlaması sonucu yükselen hava akımıdır!
If we're dealing with wind and sea, I can navigate it!
Eğer deniz ve rüzgâr varsa bu işi halledebilirim!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
Bu geminin rotacısı kim?!
It's Nami!
Sensin Nami-san!
Alright, men! Do everything Nami says!
Pekâlâ! Herkes Nami-san'ın dediğini yapsın!
– Aye!
– Hay hay!
Catch the starboard wind, turn the helm aport, and ride the current!
Rüzgârı sancaktan alıp dümeni iskeleye kırın ve akıntıyla ilerleyin!
– Aye aye!
– Başüstüne!
Oh, no! The ship is about to leave the water!
Hayır, olamaz! Gemi sudan ayrılıyor!
We're gonna fall! We're gonna fall, Nami! Do something, Nami!
Düşeceğiz! Düşeceğiz, Nami! Bir şey yap, Nami!
No, we'll make it!
Hayır, başaracağız!
We're flying!
Uçuyoruz!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Harika! Gemi uçuyor!
Is this for real?!
Haritanın sonunda beliren o efsanevi yer,
We did it!
Başardık!
Wow!
Vay be!
Nami, you're amazing!
Nami-san, muhteşemsin!
And I love you!
Ve seni seviyorum!
Go! Reach the unreachable sky!
Gidin! Ulaşılamayan göğe!
– Go!
– Gidin!
With this wind and current, we can go as high as we want!
Bu akıntı ve rüzgârla istediğimiz kadar yükseğe çıkabiliriz!
Hey, Nami! Are we almost to the sky island?!
Hey, Nami! Gökyüzü adasına yaklaştık mı?!
If it exists, it's on the other side of those clouds!
Öyle bir yer varsa, bulutların üzerindedir!
Above the clouds, huh?!
Bulutların üzerinde, ha?!
I wonder what's up there!
Orada ne var merak ediyorum!
Go right through the cumuloimperator clouds!
İmparator kümülüse gidelim!